

Profile

I am Mohammad Issa, a software engineer, a graduate of Tishreen University in Syria, Department Of Computer Engineering And Automated Control, I have a passion for programming in all its filds, especially the field artificial intelligence and its applications, I always Strive to develop my Programming Skills and gain more Experience

Interests

Interest

•

Ethical Haking, Social Media , Programming, Web

Contact

- ♠ Damascus/Syria
- **1** +963991458465
- mohammad.720y@gmail.com
- **f** /name.lastnamfacebook.com/ mohammad.aesae
- in linkedin.com/in/mohammadissa-a5216512a

MOHAMMAD HISSA

Experience

ASMA 2015 - 2018 Android Apps Devloper android studio android apps developer java programming language sql sqllite mysql

IMS 2019 - 2020 programmer

python Machine Learning Deep Learning Desktop Apps

LogiQ 2020 - 2020 Programmer

C# program Language
Visual Studio
LinQ
Sql Server
Reports
Desktop Apps
. net framework
html css js
entity framework c#
git

ALsadeem 2021 - 2021

Team Leader

Team Leader presentations communication

Education

Tishreen University

Bachelor Degree in Department Of Computer Engineering And Automated Control, Syria

Organization 2019 - 2019 Maharat min google, City Social Media Markiting

SEO SVM

Syrian Compute r Society 2019 - 2020 **Ethical Hacking , City** Ethical Hacking

Linux

Python Script

Skills

Skill group

Python
Java
Php
Deep Learning
Sql server
oracle
Laravel

Skill group

C#
Dart
Machine Learning
SQL
mysql
Flutter
android Apps
Developer

